A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
It's all right, Asherah.
I'll be by your side, watching over you and protecting you.
Like this, always and forever.
I'm falling, coming through my shadow.
Stay away,君が望めば
どんな世界も
その目に映せるから
See you in your dreams, yeah, baby
怖い夢だとしても
テレブル君のために
星を砕ぎ
飾り付けた
Black paper
信じてくれたなら
When you
Lost in your world
Forever with your soul
見上がれば
輝く
月のように
Forever with your soul
What's happening?
Everything is so confusing.
There's too much going on at one time.
I can't make sense of it all.
And right now, it's difficult to tell
what the Academy's real objective is in all this.
The Kishan's free, and the world is about to be consumed by madness.
That's where our focus should be.
After all, the Academy was founded in the first place to fight the Kishan.
That I understand.
But what about everything else they've done?
What happens now?
Trouble sleeping?
Leave me alone.
Acting like this isn't going to help you out any tomorrow.
The mission's going to be difficult enough as is.
Hey, Sol.
Huh?
Are they doing the right thing?
Who?
What are you talking about?
The Academy.
I don't understand what they're doing anymore.
They've completely stopped looking for Professor Stein.
Then there's all that other stuff Kidd told us about.
And also...
What about poor Krona?
He's still locked up in that cell.
No idea.
You know as much as I do.
Sitting in the dark and pouting isn't going to help.
Just get some sleep.
Be careful out there today, you two.
Ha!
We can handle this no problem.
We'll destroy the Kishan and be back before you even know it.
Something wrong?
Don't worry about her.
She'll snap out of it soon.
Hmm.
Let's do this.
Everyone's working so hard to stop this Kishan guy.
I want to help defeat him, too.
Yee-yow!
Charge Baba Yaga's castle.
Things are kind of gloomy.
The objective of today's mission, destroy the Kishan Asherah.
In addition, we will target those who have sided with the Kishan, including the witch Arachne and the members of her organization, Arachnophobia.
We will be launching in a time of our phase of operations.
Cover-ups, repeated without hesitation.
While they turn a blind eye to everything else but their mission.
The madness is spreading.
It must be stopped.
Before it's too late.
Which means we will also be battling against time.
Our first objective, destroy the Kishan.
Second, we obliterate the madness machine.
And then, the madness relay stations.
And finally, Arachne.
Kill her and destroy her organization.
Fine, then.
They can ignore it all if they want.
But they can't make me forget.
We have every confidence in your skills.
But we realize the risk of coming into contact with the Kishan.
So do not forget to take your doses of madness suppressing before you leave.
And now, a word from Lord Death.
Do your best, okay?
Victory, victory!
That's it.
All right.
The operation will now commence.
First destination, Baba Yaga Castle.
Excuse me, Mr. Cid.
Hmm?
There's something I wanted to ask you.
Go ahead.
It's about Krona.
What are they going to do with him?
Please tell me.
I know you know.
No.
Krona's been exiled, Maka.
He was a spy and a traitor.
He's done a lot of damage to the Academy.
Given that, exile is lenient.
Exile?
But where can he go?
When I was alive, I had tight lips.
I knew how to keep a secret.
That's the kind of man I was.
But I did talk out loud to myself at times.
Maybe Krona's exile is just a cover.
Maybe he left with Miss Marie to go after Medusa.
With Miss Marie?
But why?
Yesterday, Marie resigned.
She's no longer with the Academy.
Krona is going to settle things with Medusa once and for all.
Medusa.
It's all right.
Miss Marie will be there to back him up.
You should focus on today's operation.
We're counting on you and your anti-magic wavelength.
Don't let us down.
So that's it.
That's how they're going to handle it?
This is the adult's great solution?
Maka, I'm sorry.
What is it, Krona?
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Fine.
Then let's keep moving.
I was in the same desert not long ago.
I thought I was escaping.
This time, this time it's different.
Maka, I'm sorry I had to lie, but I'm not running anymore.
We should split our forces into thirds and make our attack on three fronts.
And the soldiers in charge of demolishing the relay stations need to synchronize their attacks so they all happen at one time.
This is the first attack on so grand a scale since the academy was founded.
That suppressant, do you really think it'll be effective against the madness?
If such a medicine actually existed, I would have delivered it throughout the world already.
I thought so.
Suppressing panic, an obvious tactic.
Lord Death, what I'd like to know is why I'm stationed here.
Yeah, that is a good question.
You were the one who made that call?
Given what we're up against, I don't think we can have too many forces in the field.
Based on my analysis, it wouldn't hurt to have all the death-sized fighting out there.
Easier said than done, Azusa.
Yikes!
We're battling a Kishin today, yet for some reason you're keeping me here
and you sent Marie and Kit off on assignments that have nothing to do with the fighting.
If you ask me, it defies common sense.
We can't know for sure what's going to happen on the battlefield today.
Surely you'll agree the best plan of action is to prepare for all possibilities.
There, you see now?
Not so simple.
Oh, dear.
Whatever they say, I still think our forces are too spread out.
Why don't you put that scary face away and come have a cup of tea?
Pull up a seat.
There's some yummy cake over here.
All right, you two!
Shake off this!
I don't know how to handle this woman.
What was that?
What's happening?
Well, I'm sure things will sort themselves out.
In the meantime, we'll focus on dealing with each new problem as it arises.
Wonderful.
I told Lord Death I wouldn't pause to accept some help.
Hi, Mr. Joe.
I'm Blair the Cat.
Starting today, I'm your new assistant.
Exciting, huh?
I'm Lisa from Chupacabra.
And my name's Arisa.
But I don't think he quite understood my request.
Meow, meow.
We are now entering arachnophobious territory.
All forces, make sure you're in place.
Ready yourselves for the attack.
Is there something bothering you, Maka?
No, it's nothing.
Uh-oh.
You're not getting cold feet, are you?
Because there's nothing to be afraid of.
Not as long as I'm here, anyway.
With a big star like me around, this is the safest place in the entire world.
If you don't quiet down, they'll know we're here.
Are you still thinking about that crap from last night?
Maybe.
You have to keep your head in the game today.
Otherwise, the whole thing will fall apart.
You of all people should know that.
Don't worry, soul.
I'm sure Maka's going to do really well today.
Sid and Lord Death both set our anti-magic wavelengths might be all we need.
They're counting on a technique I can't master.
It's ridiculous.
But there's more to it than that.
The genie hunter's not the only thing that makes you a great fighter.
There's nothing that great about me.
Damn!
Quit being such a perfectionist!
Yeah, like that'll happen!
Blackstar, will you please be quiet?
Just leave me alone, guys.
You had a conversation with Sid before we left, didn't you?
What, you mean about the genie hunter move?
I told you it's ridiculous.
No, not that.
About Miss Marie and Crona.
Do you understand what's really going on?
Why it had to be the two of them?
The DWMA made a deal with Medusa.
Because of that, we can't harm her.
Lord Death gave his word not to.
But Crona's in exile, isn't he?
And Miss Marie quit her teaching job.
Lord Death's making some pretty low moves these days.
There might be something in what Kid told us.
So maybe we really can't trust the Academy anymore.
Sol's right.
That's a sneaky plan.
I was wondering why Kid's not here with us.
Maybe this has something to do with it.
We can't afford to freak out about every little thing that comes our way right now.
If you ask me, it's the other way around.
We can't afford not to.
Don't know about you, but I'm here to win.
I'm going to take down every last one of them.
And when that's over, I'll surpass God.
Great.
Here he goes again.
What should I do?
You can sleep soundly, Asheron.
It's okay.
As long as I'm here by your side.
You'll see, my dear one.
Before much longer, the world will be utterly consumed by delicious madness.
Until then, you'll stay here with me where you'll be safe.
Lady Arachna, we have an issue.
Let's hear it.
We have detected DWMA forces.
Oh, really?
Yes, my lady.
And it appears they're searching for a way into Baba Yaga Castle.
So it would seem.
They shouldn't have been able to find the castle's location, though.
I don't think storming the castle is their only objective, either.
They seem to have deployed six additional squads to other areas.
Six forces?
They're targeting the relay stations.
The bulk of their forces will be arriving at our gates soon.
How do they know?
Medusa.
It must have been.
Prepare for a counterattack.
I want all of the troops out there.
The DWMA must be stopped, no matter what.
Right.
Hurry! Move, you maggots!
We've got a battle to fight here.
I want everyone prepared, understood?
Yes!
It's finally time.
I'm gonna grind those fools into dust.
Look at this style.
It's beginning.
We don't want to miss one minute of this.
A new world order is going to be born today.
Everything is about to change.
This is the fifth.
We're in place.
Third squadron here.
We are in position.
The seventh is ready to go.
Captain, we're ready.
All squads in place.
All right.
Listen up, everybody.
Let's go!
Rip them apart!
Triple speed, saw leg!
All clear!
Now move it!
No!
That was a familiar attack.
Looks like an old friend of mine.
Sawman.
We meet again, do we?
Ha!
Is this gonna be the last time for you, punk?
The enemy!
Commence battle at once, men!
Yeah!
I hope these guys are ready to see one hell of a performance!
Not yet, Blackstar.
Hold on.
What do you think, Maka?
The Kishin has to be defeated.
The Academy's doing the right thing.
But still, even knowing that, there's no way I can abandon Professor Stein and Krona.
That's not who I am.
We have to be careful about who at the Academy we trust.
I can't just forget about them.
But I don't know what I'm supposed to do.
What do I do?
Would you stop being such a crybaby?
Wah, wah, wah.
Whine, whine, whine.
What the hell's wrong with you?
What is your problem?
Why are you talking to me like that?
Because you have to make a decision.
Get a grip, Maka.
Decide what you're going to do.
Yes.
I see now.
You know, it's funny.
My dad always used to warn me to choose my friends wisely.
And he was right.
Look at me, a perfect student.
Thanks to you, I'm a rule breaker.
Hmph.
Right!
That's it! Sorry, Black Star. The rest is up to you.
Huh?
What's with her?
From now on, I'm gonna be doing things my way.
It's all you, man.
Hey!
Who's she kidding? Maka couldn't be more wrong.
I don't care what she says, she's still a perfect student.
Hang on, Krona. I'm coming.
Krona, I'm coming.
Come on, Krona. I'm coming.
You're playing.
What's your favorite?
I'm coming.
Come on.
Oh, my gosh.
I'm coming.
Hey!
You were helping me.
I'm coming.
THE BLOOD WORKS
jakiś
Let us see how single its conflict...
For now to solve the'reọ Yunyi yell
Where is your hope?
My hope has been niin
pirates
I've made up my mind now I just have to run to a
goal exactly sometimes in life you need to run ahead but then again
sometimes you need to stand still miss Marie to run or to stand still that is
the question
maybe I could try both at the same time work on the next episode of Soul Eater
the last magic tool mission impossible for unarmed kid watch it or I'll take
your soul